[
  {
    "id": 2.0,
    "topic": "Ports 1",
    "placeholder": 22.0,
    "solution": 22.0,
    "question": "Secure Shell (SSH)",
    "level": 1.0
  },
  {
    "id": 3.0,
    "topic": "Ports 1",
    "placeholder": 23.0,
    "solution": 23.0,
    "question": "Telnet (TELNET)",
    "level": 1.0
  },
  {
    "id": 4.0,
    "topic": "Ports 2",
    "placeholder": 53.0,
    "solution": 53.0,
    "question": "Domain Name System (DNS)",
    "level": 2.0
  },
  {
    "id": 5.0,
    "topic": "Ports 2",
    "placeholder": 67.0,
    "solution": 67.0,
    "question": "Client to server Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol v4 (DHCPv4)",
    "level": 2.0
  },
  {
    "id": 6.0,
    "topic": "Ports 2",
    "placeholder": 68.0,
    "solution": 68.0,
    "question": "Server to client Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol v4 (DHCPv4)",
    "level": 2.0
  },
  {
    "id": 7.0,
    "topic": "Ports 2",
    "placeholder": 69.0,
    "solution": 69.0,
    "question": "Trivial File Transfer Protocol (TFTP)",
    "level": 2.0
  },
  {
    "id": 8.0,
    "topic": "Ports 3",
    "placeholder": 110.0,
    "solution": 110.0,
    "question": "Post Office Protocol 3 (POP3)",
    "level": 3.0
  },
  {
    "id": 9.0,
    "topic": "Ports 3",
    "placeholder": 123.0,
    "solution": 123.0,
    "question": "Network Time Protocol (NTP)",
    "level": 3.0
  },
  {
    "id": 10.0,
    "topic": "Ports 3",
    "placeholder": 143.0,
    "solution": 143.0,
    "question": "Internet Message Access Protocol (IMAP)",
    "level": 3.0
  },
  {
    "id": 11.0,
    "topic": "Ports 3",
    "placeholder": 443.0,
    "solution": 443.0,
    "question": "Secure HTTP (HTTPS)",
    "level": 3.0
  },
  {
    "id": 12.0,
    "topic": "Ports 3",
    "placeholder": 546.0,
    "solution": 546.0,
    "question": "Client to server Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol v6 (DHCPv6)",
    "level": 3.0
  },
  {
    "id": 13.0,
    "topic": "Ports 3",
    "placeholder": 547.0,
    "solution": 547.0,
    "question": "Server to client Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol v6 (DHCPv6)",
    "level": 3.0
  },
  {
    "id": 0.0,
    "topic": "Ports 1",
    "placeholder": 20.0,
    "solution": 20.0,
    "question": "File Transfer Protocol - Data (FTP-DATA)",
    "level": 1.0
  },
  {
    "id": 1.0,
    "topic": "Ports 1",
    "placeholder": 21.0,
    "solution": 21.0,
    "question": "File Transfer Protocol - Control (FTP)",
    "level": 1.0
  }
]
